smallworlds.com 2012-11-14

# SmallWorlds Privacy Policy - SmallWorlds Forum

Your privacy is of the utmost importance to us here at SmallWorlds.  
At all times we will endeavor to protect your right to privacy, and  
only use any personal information you submit to us, for the purpose it  
was originally intended for.

The following policy describes how we treat personal information that we collect and receive, including information related to your use  
of the SmallWorlds service. Personal information is information about  
you that is personally identifiable like your name, email address, or  
date of birth, and that is not otherwise publicly available.

If we make any significant changes to the privacy policy, we will  
notify you via email or by placing a prominent notice on our site and  
within the SmallWorlds entry process.

## Information Collection

SmallWorlds collects personal information when you register with us,  
when you use the SmallWorlds service, and when you visit SmallWorlds  
website pages or the pages of some of our partners. We may combine  
information about you that we have with information we obtain from  
business partners or other companies. We generally use this information  
to improve the relevance and quality of our service.

When you register we ask for information such as your name, email  
address, date of birth etc. We use this information to allow you to log  
into the SmallWorlds service, and to contact you for important  
communications regarding the SmallWorlds service. You can opt out of  
these communications at any time.

SmallWorlds collects information about your transactions with us and with some of our business partners.

SmallWorlds will never store credit card information or other  
sensitive payment details. When you choose to "save this card" during  
our payment process, our bank stores the information in their secure  
systems.

Our server logs automatically record information from your browser,  
including your IP address, browser cookie information, and the pages  
you request. Cookies are small text files placed in your web browser to  
remember your preferences, and are generally used to determine how many  
visitors we get and what parts of our website and service they visit.

SmallWorlds does not currently accept registrations from children of the age of 12 or under.

SmallWorlds allows third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our web site. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit [networkadvertising.org](http://networkadvertising.org/). 

## Information Sharing

SmallWorlds will not disclose any personal information about you to  
any third parties without your permission, except under the following  
circumstances:

  * We provide information to trusted partners who work on behalf of or  
with SmallWorlds under confidentiality agreements. These companies will  
only use this information in context to their relationship with  
SmallWorlds, and will not be allowed to use it for their own  
independent purposes.
  * We are required by law to divulge the information, or in the  
process of exercising our legal rights or to defend against legal  
claims. We may also share information in order to prevent or arrest any  
illegal activities, violations of SmallWorld's Terms Of Service, or any  
other activity that may threaten the safety or security of any person.
  * We may transfer or merge information if we are acquired by, or merged with, another company.
